[opening theme music playing]
THE TRUNK
[ominous music playing]
[loud rattling]
[thunder rumbling]
[phone buzzing]
[phone line ringing]
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed cannot be reached.
At the tone, please record your message.
[disconnect tone]
[keys rattle]
You could invent a decent excuse
before you go to his house!
You can't just burst in there.
Move now.
I don't have time to argue
with a fake husband.
[door slams]
[thunder rumbling]
[gentle piano music playing]
[gentle piano music continues]
[woman breathes heavily]
[sniffling]
- [siren wailing]
- [panting]
[thunder rumbling]
[gentle piano music continues]
[music fades]
- [thunder rumbles]
- [door closes]
Go ahead, say it.
This better be a confession.
What did In-ji say?
That I had cameras inserted into it?
Well, yes, that's true.
Sorry. I didn't know it was a crime
to observe you like that.
I had no choice. I was going crazy.
Look, I wanted us to get back together.
I just needed to see you yearning,
you know?
Still longing for me,
even when In-ji was around you.
Are you saying you did this so
you and I could be together again?
You told the doctors
to save the child's life, knowing I'd die,
as I was getting wheeled into the OR.
How could you do that to me?
How could sweet Jeong-won do that?
When you walked into the street that day,
I blamed you and wanted you to know.
I felt horrible
for our child.
All I wanted was to die with it.
After I got pregnant,
every goddamn day, every second, was hell.
It felt like I was suddenly the most
useless person in the whole world.
I was withering away
because I dreaded having to give birth
to that child more than death.
But you… [sobs softly]
…you were just excited.
It was giving you
some new sense of purpose. [sniffles]
All of a sudden, I was
some limp appendage
carrying your child, nothing more.
Do you know what that's like?
Then why didn't you just say it, huh?!
You should've told me
you weren't cut out for it!
And I always would've been haunted
seeing how disappointed you were.
Moms are only supposed to ask them
to save the child first, right?
And I hated myself then too.
Soon, I wanted
anything maternal in me to die.
I blamed myself for not understanding
how you were feeling back then.
I thought I was being
a total self-involved idiot.
That's how I dealt with this.
And I thought all of it would go away
if you and I could be together
like we used to.
But how could you
do what my father did to us?
I was scared. I didn't know what to do.
I didn't have the same kind
of power over you that I used to.
Jeong-won,
we're still accomplices, right?
I killed our child,
and you killed your mother, didn't you?
Since we've both done awful things,
maybe we can atone together.
The two of us. Hmm?
You're demented, Seo-yeon.
I'm going to atone.
Just not by your side.
That's over for good now.
[thunder rumbling]
[door opens]
- [sobs]
- [door closes]
[whimpers]
[crying]
[somber piano music playing]
[crying continues]
[somber piano music continues]
You wanna get out of the city?
[gasps]
[thunder rumbling]
[somber piano music continues]
[music fades]
[footsteps approaching]
I'm sure you knew there were cameras.
Why'd you stay quiet?
Well, I mean,
I didn't know how to break it to you.
I should have taken care of it.
I didn't want you to know.
I'm sorry I kept this from you.
I'm tired of excuses.
You turned a blind eye to the whole thing
'cause you didn't want
trouble in the marriage.
You should know I didn't shrug it off.
I actually grabbed Seo-yeon by her hair
and roughed her up a little.
Really? You… you hit Seo-yeon?
I clobbered her.
Those blue pills taped to the record…
When I found out what they were, I…
I pretty much went
berserk on her, you know?
If I wanted to, I could've broken
two or three of her ribs, so you know.
Jujitsu pays off, as it turns out.
Man, I wish I'd seen that.
You might've had to take a side.
[romantic piano music playing]
[chuckles]
You actually attacked Seo-yeon?
[laughs] Crazy. You pulled her hair
and punched her.
[both laughing]
[romantic piano music continues]
[Jeong-won] It's a whole family.
I wanna go get some groceries.
We should get a little banchan
and a few cold ones.
We'll banter together as we go.
We'll be like, "Do we need all this?"
Or, "Let's not do ground coffee.
Whole bean's good."
Do you have a favorite dish?
Would you mind if I cooked?
[music fades]
How long are you gonna be
living in that house?
If I were you…
Let's go.
What was that, huh?
"If I were you…" You'd what?
[chuckles] You know,
you shouldn't do that.
- Stop yourself like that.
- [laughs]
[melodic piano music playing]
- Mm.
- What is it?
What is it, huh?
[melodic piano music continues]
[In-ji chuckles]
♪ You don't have to stay ♪
♪ Just let the past decay ♪
♪ 'Cause I know it's not your fault ♪
♪ You think you're not enough ♪
♪ But I know we'll make it through ♪
♪ Just escape from the darkness ♪
♪ I won't let you drown ♪
♪ I can pull you out of shadows ♪
♪ Just hold my hand, and we'll be fine ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Baby, I'll be your savior ♪
♪ What if we die? ♪
♪ We cannot be happy
If there's nothing to lose ♪
♪ What if we try ♪
♪ To stay alive? ♪
♪ Will we ever be free from the past? ♪
♪ What do we live for? ♪
♪ Mm-mm ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm ♪
♪ So what do we live for? ♪
[music fades]
No, keep your hand there.
I'll warm it for you.
I was sure about you from day one.
[In-ji] Han Jeong-won is my husband.
[camera shutter clicks]
[photographer] All right.
Look this way, please.
One, two…
[camera shutter clicks]
[Jeong-won] The mausoleum,
the graduation ceremony…
That was a pretty rough day, honestly.
I felt like you were the only one
who could understand
what I had been going through.
If I had gotten to know you in those days…
if we'd met back then,
how would it have turned out?
[Jeong-won sighs]
[wistful music playing]
We might've broken up
or drifted apart quickly.
I mean, who knows.
I just…
I'm almost certain
I would've recognized you
even if we saw each other here and there.
I feel something strong here.
And I know I wanna be with you.
[sighs]
I want a divorce.
We're here 'cause I wanted to end things.
Did I do… something wrong?
Is there an actual problem here?
Jeong-won, this marriage is a failure.
And it's my fault. I crossed a boundary.
At this point, I don't…
I don't have a reason
to keep our relationship going,
so I should
stop it right now.
[scoffs]
It's time to be real, okay?
Acting all cold and aloof…
bringing up the manual.
It's a lie 'cause deep down, you're
desperate for something to hold onto.
Haven't you been marrying yourself off
because you… you couldn't survive
being alone for much longer?
We're both
incredibly fragile human beings.
That's why our lives are a mess.
So, for once, would you stop talking
about boundaries and just…
just admit it to me, will you?
Just say it. You're falling for me too.
I told you I stepped over the line.
Sorry that doesn't mean you have become
a significant person in my life.
It's over. Do you understand, Jeong-won?
[wind whistling]
[melodic acoustic guitar music playing]
[device beeps]
[melodic acoustic guitar music continues]
[Jeong-won] If we'd met back then,
how would it have turned out?
If I had gotten to know you in those days…
I'm almost certain
I would've recognized you
even if we saw each other here and there.
[Seo-yeon] Although, for a low-rent whore,
you really have an amazing ability
to bring bad luck to everyone around.
[Tae-seong] Would you give me attention,
In-ji, if I murdered Jeong-won?
[Seo-yeon] Why bullshit Jeong-won?
[In-ji] Don't get me wrong.
I'm not hesitating out of respect for you.
[Seo-yeon] I guess you don't want
Jeong-won to get hurt, do you?
You're a fake. We know it's true.
[melodic acoustic guitar music continues]
[man] You sure I can just have it?
Why are you giving it up?
Thanks for opening early
on all those mornings so I could go.
Well, I'll see you around soon.
Hopefully, the weather clears up.
Uh, no.
I'll be gone for good.
[music fades]
[Jeong-won] Hey, are you in there?
Open the door, In-ji!
Noh In-ji, you there?
Jesus, quiet!
Mr. Han?
[door lock beeps]
[inhales sharply]
[exhales sharply]
Hold this.
[beeping]
[door lock beeps]
Welcome.
You can keep your shoes on.
[door lock beeps]
[coffee machine beeps]
[coffee pouring]
Oh. Thank you.
Well, you seem normal.
Well, uh, you… don't know me,
so why are you…
Well, I'd guess you're in love with her,
and it's driving you nuts.
Can you tell me where she is?
[chuckles]
You should know. How would I know?
You're married, aren't you?
I'm sure she's off somewhere
worrying about you as we speak.
[inhales sharply]
Look for her yourself.
She's finished
with the guy who owns this flat.
Hmm. I appreciate the drink.
Lovebirds, huh?
- Could we move things a little faster?
- Yes, sir.
And please get rid of
the broken fixture ASAP.
- That's the priority.
- We're on it.
- Okay, thanks. And keep it up.
- Of course.
We need to get this done fast.
[uneasy music playing]
[man 2] Let's get to the glass first.
[uneasy music continues]
[music intensifies]
[man] She said she was done kayaking.
Seemed pretty sure about it.
Even gave me her paddles.
Um, would you just reach out
if you ever see her around here again?
[paper tears]
[man] Sure.
[sighs]
[phone buzzing]
NM LEE SEON
Um, hello?
This is Lee Seon.
The contract you had with us
has been cut short. I'm sorry.
As you may know,
you are entitled to request
financial damages from us
if you'd like to do so.
[Jeong-won] Oh, no. I won't be doing that.
Uh, just make sure
that no harm comes to Ms. Noh.
Yes. We'll see to it, Mr. Han.
Uh… the two of us talked.
Mostly as friends.
I just wish I knew more about her.
If you know where she might be or…
how I can reach her, please tell me.
Now that your contract's inactive,
I can't give you more details
regarding Noh In-ji, I'm afraid.
Sorry about that.
[pensive piano music playing]
[disconnect tone]
[pensive piano music continues]
Well, he isn't suing us.
No case for breach of contract, no fines.
That's a relief.
Look, I need you to protect Jeong-won.
Even if it's not… in NM's interest
to take those kinds of precautions.
It's strange, you doing this.
The contract's done for you two.
You're both taking care of each other.
Goodbye.
Around two years into my own marriage,
I almost ended up killing my husband.
When it's good,
marriage is a transaction, In-ji.
Do you think you are… really in love?
Are you scared?
Enough to terminate your marriage?
[Ji-o] Nice to see you here.
Feels like we're coworkers.
Welcome to the sad little soiree
of spurned exes and rejects.
I happened to like my marriage.
Now, thanks to you, there's a stain
on my otherwise stellar record.
And also, I'm in trouble
with the company's COO.
[phone buzzing]
[unsettling music playing]
[Tae-seong] Hello? Finally! Why would you
leave your phone off like that?
This thing's hard to open.
Harder than I thought.
It's got a double lock,
which means two sets of combinations.
Just some extra security.
[chuckles] It's nice, huh?
The trunk, I mean.
I've got it right here.
Just can't open the fucking thing.
You mean you just…
Tae-seong, did you steal the trunk?
Hmm, I guess I did.
But now what do I do?
Should I take the contract
you're hiding inside of it
and reveal it to the whole world?
Or should I kill Jeong-won first?
Two options. Come on, pick.
That contract is done now.
Listen, I'm not involved with him.
It's completely over.
How come?
Because of me?
[chuckles softly]
I'll take care of Jeong-won. Okay, In-ji?
The contract is over. Okay, Tae-seong?
Not yet, it isn't.
This didn't happen before.
I remember you
with those men you didn't love.
It was good for us.
Now you don't care at all!
[breathes deeply]
I can't stand Jeong-won
and those damn suits you work for
at that company. They did this to me!
NM's trying to get me committed
to a mental hospital again.
Maybe they'll try to off me this time.
Who knows? Huh?
[chuckles]
Since it's come to this,
I will need a backup plan. Ya know?
Please. I'll… I'll unlock it for you.
[sighs]
I'm in. Where should we meet?
[unsettling music continues]
[disconnect tone]
[Ji-o] Seo-yeon. Seo-yeon.
Seo-yeon! Seo-yeon, wake up!
Let's do a gastric lavage.
Full blood panel. And call the cops.
Hey, wake up, Seo-yeon.
You need to wake up, Seo-yeon!
Come on, Seo-yeon.
[music fades]
[Ji-o] I guess it's come to this.
Is this what you wanted?
She's always been kinda unhinged,
you know?
She said she wants to live with you.
Well, that's crazy.
You know what will
happen to her, Jeong-won?
She will OD just to prove a point to us.
Can you live with that?
[melancholy music playing]
My guess is I can't persuade you, so…
so go through with it
if that's what you want.
Sorry, Ji-o.
And don't call me. I'll be busy today.
[car engine starts]
[glass clinks]
[music fades]
I thought I would be comfortable.
Take the room down here.
Acting like a little boy
is gonna wear you down.
We're even now, aren't we?
[pants]
Look, I let you into my house again
'cause I wanted to give you a second.
A second to accept the hard truth.
I've always wondered why
I couldn't bring myself to leave you.
I realized it's because I pitied you.
Seo-yeon, listen.
There is no going back for us.
Neither one of us.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[glass shatters]
[breathing heavily]
[stirring music playing]
[Si-jeong] Wait. Are you seriously going?
What are you gonna do by yourself?
I'll head over right now.
Tell me where you are.
Si-jeong… I think
I have screwed up everything.
You're saying…
Maybe it's all my fault. All of it.
Hye-yeong. Do-ha too.
And Jeong-won.
[groans] What the hell?
Come on! That makes no sense!
Hey, In-ji! Oh, come on!
In-ji, hey! Don't say that!
[disconnect tone]
[phone line ringing]
NOH IN-JI
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed cannot be reached.
At the tone--
NOH IN-JI
[phone buzzing]
HAN JEONG-WON
[uneasy music playing]
[grass rustling]
[trunk clatters]
All alone tonight? You're brave, huh?
Should I be afraid right now, Tae-seong?
No. Not you, lovely In-ji.
- All right, I'll open it up for you.
- Whoa, slow down.
Hey, come on. What's the hurry?
I mean, we just got here.
Okay. So the contract and the manual,
it's all in here?
It's evidence.
What's with that look? Are you afraid
if you say the combination,
you'll end up like Do-ha?
You're afraid people will
point fingers at you?
You seem kinda excited that I might
get into serious trouble, Tae-seong.
Honestly, making it official
is the best-case scenario anyway.
Then I'll be the only thing you have left.
[Tae-seong chuckles]
You saw it back then… with Do-ha.
How would it benefit you?
Think about this.
Being stuck to my side,
sharing my suffering.
There's still time to turn this around.
Just go move on with your life, Tae-seong.
Just leave me be,
and I swear I'll forget all about this.
The thing is…
I won't suffer like you.
I mean, what do I care if you're miserable
and your life is in shambles as long as
you stay with me forever, In-ji?
Sounds like a good life.
[chuckles]
I killed this pharmacist not too long ago.
Pretty sure I told you about that.
You remember I killed a person?
Turns out it's a lot easier
than I thought.
As for the cops,
they still have no idea who did it.
[chuckles]
[unsettling music playing]
[tires squeal]
[Tae-seong] I'm night-kayaking
with Ms. Noh right now. Care to join us?
Crazy ass.
NOH IN-JI
[phone line ringing]
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed cannot be reached.
[disconnect tone]
- [tires squeal]
- [engine roars]
[unsettling music continues]
What's wrong?
Where did…
where did you find this, Tae-seong?
Where do you think?
Jeong-won's house. The closet.
In his room.
[eerie music sting]
[unsettling music resumes]
[Tae-seong] What's the problem?
Well, I don't know.
It looks like the lock is jammed
because, uh,
you tried to break it off first.
Oh, give me a fucking break.
You have got to be fucking kidding me!
Jesus Christ!
Tomorrow we can just take it into a store.
They'll take care of it for us.
In-ji, do you think I'm a fool? Huh?!
[breathing nervously]
Come on. What the hell do you want?
You could've brought it to me right away.
And you should've brought it right to me,
but you busted it like an idiot!
[yells] God-fucking-damn it!
[grunts]
Oh shit!
[grunting]
[straining] Open up!
[grunts] Fucking thing!
Fuck!
Will you stop with the manic nonsense
if I'm dead and gone?
Eom Tae-seong, let's…
let's die together, the two of us.
Come on. That's a nice idea, right?
[sighs]
Well, holy shit.
You've been working on your jokes.
You really had me for a second.
[Tae-seong chuckles]
Hmm, but we can't die tonight.
Option number two is good.
[stirring music playing]
Number two?
[stirring music continues]
[car door opens and closes]
[stirring electronic music playing]
Hey, In-ji? In-ji!
You know,
if I were to kill someone,
I'd just go back to the hospital.
[Jeong-won] Can you hear me?
Why are you doing this?
God, what the hell is wrong with you?
[Jeong-won] In-ji!
Just because.
- There's no reason in particular.
- In-ji, where are you?
- [Jeong-won] In-ji, hang on!
- [In-ji breathing nervously]
Sh!
In-ji, are… are you all right?
Stay back, Jeong-won. Just stay back.
[grunts]
[In-ji panting]
[In-ji screams]
[grunting]
[Tae-seong] Die.
[all grunting]
[music swells]
[breathing nervously]
[stirring music playing]
[both panting]
[In-ji grunts]
[In-ji breathing frantically]
[Tae-seong grunts]
[In-ji breathing heavily]
[In-ji screams]
[both panting]
It's over. It's over.
You're gonna be okay.
I shot Tae-seong.
I did. I swear I… I shot…
[exhales sharply] It's okay.
What matters is you're safe.
I shot…
[In-ji whimpers]
[panting]
[In-ji sobs]
[In-ji panting, sobbing]
[both breathing heavily]
[In-ji panting]
[Jeong-won] It's okay.
[stirring music continues]
[engine starts]
[music fades]
Weren't there live rounds in the gun?
I thought I'd kill myself
if I left it loaded, and…
and I guess I should have.
I should've killed him myself.
[wistful music playing]
You had no reason.
It's my issue, not yours.
I did not put myself
in the middle of this for you.
That's just not the case.
I can keep both of us safe. We'll be fine.
Glad to hear it.
Keep yourself safe, then, Jeong-won.
Go right ahead.
And I can handle the rest, all right?
In-ji…
[sighs]
I just want this to be over.
I'm…
so tired of all of it.
[wistful music continues]
[sighs]
[man inhales deeply]
So they were blanks,
and you fired in self-defense?
[music fades]
Well, despite that fact,
you'll still be charged
for the possession of an illegal weapon.
Understand?
Yes.
[groans]
So tell me,
who do you think killed Tae-seong?
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music continues]
[engine sputtering]
Shit.
[grunts]
[grunting continues]
[gasps, groans]
[screams]
[breathing frantically]
[tense music playing]
[boat approaching]
[music intensifies]
[blade slices]
[tense music continues]
[tense music swells]
[unsettling music playing]
[Seon] I can't help but think
you're the ideal choice
for this task, Ji-o.
Eom Tae-seong.
Think you can take care of it for us?
[unsettling music continues]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[music subsides]
I admit I've been wrong about all of this.
I think you are the one I need.
I'm saying you finally won.
[uneasy music playing]
The blade's not usually like this, right?
Uh…
What have you been up to, Ji-o?
I'm afraid I…
killed someone earlier.
I was a guard for NM.
[uneasy music continues]
I was there when Tae-seong killed
that other keeper years ago…
but I ran away.
[music fades]
That stuck with me,
and it's been bothering me ever since.
But that wasn't the only reason I did it.
I liked being married to you.
[wistful music playing]
I'll move out soon and leave you alone.
[wistful music continues]
[man] So why is it that Eom Tae-seong had
your trunk in his possession, Mrs. Lee?
Who knows?
I rarely used that trunk
'cause it was so difficult to unlock.
And that's why you left it at Jeong-won's?
Something like that, I guess.
He was killed with a very long,
pointy weapon that left a precise wound.
There was a single hole.
Now, what kind of sound does that make?
Sounds like a length of rebar.
I've seen those sharpened into stakes
at construction sites.
Uh, no.
Smoother than that.
That would be too dull.
There are lots of things like that.
[music fades]
I don't know why you'd ask me
such a specific question.
If there are no more questions,
can I go now?
I'm really tired.
Well, we've already pored over
the trunk's contents.
You should take a look as well
to make sure everything's still there.
If you say
an item's missing at a later time,
we won't be able to help, that's all.
[stirring music playing]
[stirring music continues]
[door closes]
Hey, so the realtor said that…
it's a buyer's market,
and they had to
lower the price to rent it.
Take good care of these guys.
You've got a great track record with that.
Think about cutting back on
the amount of coffee you drink.
Stop lecturing me.
Take care, okay?
What's wrong?
Will you live happily ever after
with that prick?
What is it?
I hope NM keeps you busy
with another young wife.
[chuckles]
I had a feeling you knew the truth
about me all along, In-ji.
God, you're something else.
[chuckles] You're the worst.
Well, I should've just
come out with it sooner.
To think I spent all that time
beating myself up. Fuck me.
I'll get going.
[Do-dam] "This too shall pass."
Don't forget it.
That's all there is to married life.
You can trust me.
I've been divorced three times.
[sentimental music playing]
[sentimental music continues]
So is that everything you brought?
A trunkload
is all you need for a marriage.
I wonder why it never crossed my mind
to just leave this house.
Was I afraid?
I think you're just lazy.
The thing is, moving requires diligence.
Squabbling with the old landlord,
get a new fridge, a new kitchen table,
not to mention
you have to find the new curtains.
Hey, you are one to talk, you know.
Because if I were you, I would have…
I would've left that flat a while ago.
I doubt that.
[music fades]
So you're…
really gonna tear down this house?
Why?
I guess I'm too soft
to squabble with an old landlord.
I know I'll get tired of something new
and come crawling back here,
so I need to get to the root of this
and just burn it down.
[thud]
You're gonna demolish it anyway. Come on.
[melodic piano music playing]
♪ You don't have to stay ♪
♪ Just let the past decay ♪
♪ 'Cause I know it's not your fault ♪
♪ You think you're not enough… ♪
What were you gonna say to me?
The night you said, "If I were you."
Was this it?
That you wanted me
to get out of this house?
You've been thinking about that?
Is that the reason you're doing this?
So you were not saying that?
I was just talking…
about how you should…
rent it out.
Basically, I was saying
I'd use the money from renting it out
to travel if I owned the house.
I didn't think you'd do
something like this.
Ah, renting it out.
♪ Mm-mm ♪
♪ What do we live for… ♪
Do you think you might stay with me…
if we see each other down the road?
Who knows?
We could… be destined to be together.
I mean, probably not forever.
I could do, like, three decades.
[In-ji chuckles]
And what if we run into each other
two times in a row?
♪ Calling you again and again… ♪
Look, if it happens twice,
that's providence.
♪ All the clouds and storms before us… ♪
So two times.
Would it do?
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Baby, I'll be your savior… ♪
I'm grateful for everything you've done.
♪ What if we die… ♪
I need you to know that
no matter what the future brings.
♪ What if we try ♪
♪ To stay alive? ♪
♪ Will we ever be free from the past? ♪
♪ You know I am your savior ♪
♪ Holding you so close… ♪
[music ends]
DEAD BODY DISCOVERED AT LAKE
MURDER SUSPECT TAKEN INTO CUSTODY
- [stirring music playing]
- [reporters clamoring]
[camera shutters clicking]
[connect tone]
[phone line ringing]
Hi. Mr. Choi, listen.
I think I have a case for you.
Yoon-a asked me to check in
on the remodel. That's why I'm here.
You don't need to explain yourself.
I know, but… I can't help it.
You know that.
[music fades]
Ji-o and I are renewing our contract.
And I'm hiring a top-notch lawyer.
Seo-yeon.
I thought I was being suffocated,
and it was your fault.
But now I think I was
holding you back from what you wanted.
I never explained
why things weren't working.
I should've been honest.
Well, I was the villain.
That's how I got my closure with you.
It hurts my pride less to think that.
[melodic acoustic guitar music playing]
[melodic acoustic guitar music continues]
Momo. Hey, Mo. Momo.
You're sleepy, huh?
[chuckles]
Hey, Cookie.
[melodic acoustic guitar music continues]
[sighs]
Yeah, I'm lonely.
[melodic acoustic guitar music continues]
ITERATION
[woman in film breathing heavily]
[screams]
[panting fearfully]
DIRECTED BY NOH SU-HWAN
SCREENPLAY BY YANG JEONG-WON
MUSIC BY HAN JEONG-WON
[music fades]
[phone buzzes]
What?
[Hyeon-cheol] Hey, man.
So the film finally got released.
Only ten months late.
The reviews are lukewarm.
Makes sense.
Does anyone actually go to the theater
to watch B-horror movies nowadays?
I know you're not fishing,
so stop moping around, will you?
- Come back to work.
- I'm not at the lake.
Get back here, dude.
I think my wife's leaving me.
Not as bad as you think.
[disconnect tone]
- [Hyeon-cheol] What is this again?
- [Yoon-a] Divorce papers.
I've been filling them out
a little every day.
Why's that?
The only way I can get any space is taking
you and the kids out of the equation.
How do you not have space?
I gave you exclusive rights
to the bathroom 'cause you're constipated.
You think I have space?
You've got a name, right?
Oh Hyeon-cheol. You have a job, don't you?
What about me? I have nothing.
I'm just a mother and your wife.
You have a nice office
with a plaque and a big desk.
I have a big circle of friends,
and no one else is married, you know that?
They're all happy, doing amazing things.
Meanwhile, I've accomplished nothing.
I don't know where my life's going.
And I get it, okay?
Someone has to raise the kids
and take care of them. I know that.
[breathes heavily]
I just-- I…
[sobs]
I just don't think that I'm happy
with that choice at all, and…
[crying]
[sighs]
Maybe you should get a laser treatment.
I'll give you a card.
Mine, not the company card.
Why can't we even have
a serious conversation?
Are you not capable of that?!
Wow. Just 3,000?
I can give you a lot more, you know.
That's all right. That amount's fine.
A little odd
to turn down a better offer, hmm? [laughs]
No dead bodies in here, right?
[woman cackles]
Just kidding. Here ya go.
[woman laughs]
- Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
[woman] Oh yeah. You bet. I always do.
What a beauty. My gosh. Mm!
[woman hisses]
What am I gonna do with you, huh?
What an incredible design. Mm.
[woman laughs]
AMERICANO 3,000 WON
[woman] Thanks so much. Enjoy.
[In-ji] Have a nice day.
[romantic pop music playing]
[romantic pop music continues]
Uh… I was just taking my cat
over to the vet.
One of his paws was a bit sore, and…
Oh, right. I do have a…
I do have a few cats now.
Oh.
Everything going okay?
It was pretty scary.
I saw your movie.
You see the credits, by any chance?
That's the whole reason I went.
It's number one, In-ji.
Our first chance encounter.
One more to go before we get it right.
Yeah.
[romantic pop music continues]
[music fades]